你是想当领头羊  还是想跟着走
Do you want to lead or do you want to follow?
-他想跟着走  -跟都懒得跟
- He wants to follow.  - And barely that.
进来
Come in.
-这是我的办公室  -无人机袭击
- It's my office.  - Drone strike.
-难以置信  -无人机袭击
- I don't believe this.  - Drone strike.
-这位是杰利·丹塔纳  -又一次吗
- This is Jerry Dantana.  - There was another one?
-今天早上  -什么东西
- This morning.  - What you got there?
无人机袭击
Drone strike. Drone strike.
听不懂你在说什么
Can't understand what you're saying.
你当然懂  路透社
You can too understand what I'm... Reuters.
我说的就是这个
This is what I was talking...
美军"掠夺者"无人机袭击巴基斯坦西北部的车辆
United States Predator drone strikes vehicle in northwest Pakistan.
-我能看看吗  -这是张白纸
- Can I see that?  - It's a blank piece of paper.
我把报道留在办公室里了
I left the wire report in my office
在路上  我觉得应该拿个道具
and on the way here, I decided I wanted a prop.
你就没想到找人打印出来吗
You didn't think to just have someone print it out?
现在很多更好的想法都冒出来了
A lot of better ideas are coming to me as I'm standing here,